The Guide to the Jerome Charyn Papers 1937-1997 MSS.044
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XI: Publishers Catalogs
  - Miscellaneous, 1964-1997; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Mysterious Press, 1992-1995; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Rotbush, 1992; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - St. Martin's Press, 2000; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Serpent's Tail, 1990-1994; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Series XII: Events
  - American Thriller Special at Cologne, 1991; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Annual Festival of the Strand 6th), Galveston, Texas, 1977; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Banquet du Livre, 1995; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bascove Exhibition, 1995; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The City as a Novel, 1991; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Davis Festival of the Arts, 1967; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Documentaire, 1992; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ecrivains Presents, 1995; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Festival International du Livre de Saint-Malo (5e, 8e), 1994-1997; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Festival du Livre de Jeunesse de Cherbourg (10e), 1997; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - La Fureur de Lire, 1991; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Les Boreales de Normandie, 1997; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Mystery Writers Annual, 1993; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Travelling 100 Villes - 6e Festival de Cinema de Rennes, 1995; 31142040613773 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Series XIII: Audiovisual Materials and Ephemera
  - Subseries A: Videotapes Vasanta Productions, Inc The good policeman
    - Shoot Day # 1, March 29, 1993, Scenes: 75, 27, 67. Total running time: 40:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_eaaabe3ec90cd297178ddcb674b76940)
    - Shoot Day # 2, March 30, 1993, Scenes: 19, 26, 41. (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_0fe894c716fa625769352e923cc5a6c2)
    - Shoot Day # 3, March 31, 1993, Scenes: 40, 62. Total running time: 28:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_d01d3bb9a27c451bfc0d23e436ab1abb)
    - Shoot Day # 4, April 1, 1993, Scenes: 38, 39, 68, 73, A41. Total running time: 14:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_ab0154fd06c906fc0e2d92b259041ce9)
    - Shoot Day # 5, April 2, 1993, Scenes: 69, 74, 2nd Unit. Total running time: 60:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_1e49fbb07ac16ef4b565c9cdd7cf57d7)
    - Shoot Day # 6, April 5, 1993, Scenes: 21, 20, B14. Total running time: 41:00 + Shoot Day # 4 (Retransfer), Scenes A41 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_832de0fb9610416f41b286572d8cdc98)
    - Shoot Day # 7, April 6, 1993, Scenes: 63, 85, 85A, 9, 45, 72. Total running time: 40:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_c312c2bc53f287948eb463cf01efdd41)
    - Shoot Day # 8, April 7, 1993, Scenes: 6, 63A, 85A. Total running time: 52:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_8aa7fc31f0a7045ae84516b38674b040)
    - Shoot Day # 9, April 8, 1993, Scenes: 7C - 7M, 8, 11, 12, 7N, 13, 7P-7S, 15, 14. Total running time: 40:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_27ca4647abd8366d51705f01ed1191c4)
    - Shoot Day # 10, April 9, 1993, Scenes: 29, D29-A29. Total running time: 46:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_4a2e404c6485a60539ed822522e4571f)
    - Shoot Day # 11, April 12, 1993, Scenes: 25, 16. Total running time: 33:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_01925c1e047a4159a9dbd302e678b4d5)
    - Shoot Day # 12, April 13, 1993, Scenes: 55, 56. Total running time: 60:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_2efb10b7edcf6c483a7c1358f0f7f201)
    - Shoot Day # 13, April 14, 1993, Scenes: 64, E21, A21. Total running time: 50:00 + Retransfer scenes: 56, 56A - 56C (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_178911d5b578c478df83e7560f49d55f)
    - Shoot Day # 14, April 15, 1993, Scenes: 86, 44, 47, 79. Total running time: 26:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_eff6808847f2a0f8296159ef86e0a3ed)
    - Shoot Day # 15, April 16, 1993, Scenes: A77, 33, 47, 78, 35. Total running time: 45:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_203ff8b6f746957431a9bd77116cc9b1)
    - Shoot Day # 16, April 19, 1993, Part 1 of 2, Scenes: 29, 24, 28, 22, 23. Total running time: 57:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_eeeb57b456e958a7e94566164e10adbf)
    - Shoot Day # 16, April 19, 1993, Part 2 of 2, Scenes: 29, 24. Total running time: 57:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_9757f34b4d92baf5105462a85143721e)
    - Shoot Day # 17, April 20, 1993, Scenes: 32, 34, 36. Total running time: 39:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_b92ffab607a98a9c9d67708ff8ba82e4)
    - Shoot Day # 18, April 21, 1993, Scenes: B21-D21. Total running time: 8:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_06547fd7357c47d6084ff5c214db6a37)
    - Shoot Day # 19, April 23, 1993, Scenes: 83, 82. Total running time: 68:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_e1601dd54832f9187de260eee5beff9b)
    - Shoot Day # 20, April 23, 1993, Scenes: 2. Total running time: 13:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_21ec138ce0b43de9aa4faa8609be9ed5)
    - Shoot Day # 21, April 27, 1993, Part 1 of 2, Scenes: 3, 1, 80. Total running time: 60:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_ff7055895c6a611e384d6750474ae78d)
    - Shoot Day # 21, April 27, 1993, Part 2 of 2, Scenes: 1G-1L. Total running time: 27:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_6a02b2dc23f403bc7e2d05cb820f193b)
    - Temp Dub for Network Screening, May 12, 1993, Acts 1-7. Running time 81:00 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_36d75e6858d58898f0fa091adfd7cb28)
  - Subseries B: Other Videotapes
    - Circle de Niuuit(?), January 27, 1997 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_e8f870a8e1a4f2a08ad5cc070ec0a93b)
    - Jerome Charyn Interview, November 18, 1995 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_1dd09241a7e43e81d80e0737bed8a200)
    - Jerome Charyn - Portrait of the Artist-Pilot-WNYC, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_ebfa0129187e17f343bb5de11ae7cff2)
    - CNN on Good Policeman, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_a75eb44d2793d5f06e58b9c7f29808a5)
    - Ernest Hemingway, Une bruyante solitude, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_8c4bb051324a7f57ad423f921f9f7a91)
    - Ex Libris Charyn, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_05318c3a2587843f5bf863085ec2fb42)
    - Museen der Welt, Ellis Island, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_dc6755b3680c7336769ba4b19ad799a9)
    - Sent ans de bulles - 1 of 2, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_d70aa45325741f6ec3547f3e20242a14)
    - Sent ans de bulles - 2 of 2, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_04abe0f5dd022c61e52037854ca9afe1)
    - Swiss National TV, Culture Magazine "Next", April 13, 1997, Jefe/Charyn "Madame Lambert" (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_76a34e736711f4ad8dc2854e2cd40569)
  - Subseries C: Other Media Types
    - Floppy Disk "The GOod Policeman Series, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_864bcd4bac0f15ff05adcfcd48e2778c)
    - Floppy Disk "Word Star 4.2 - Film Type 1", undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_95e568446c4daf4b11ae3f27cd4be402)
    - 1 roll of film, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_2ba9c4e295ab3cc9cdf5138e12e72ad6)
    - Audiotape "Un livre des voix:", undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_b5630bf86e013353ecdafea4637c0b32)
    - Audiotape "Gentle Jack, 3 versions", undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_ac00cc480d49559436a6381bd310b976)
    - Untitled Audiotape, undated (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_7c55b9034b63ad27002f823138b58bc6)
- Series XIV: Miscellaneous
  - Album (with Postcards), undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Book Proposals, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Charyn/Boucq, "Bocca del diavolo", photocopies from Comic Art, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Charyn/Boucq, Du Ventre de la Bete - New York, 1993; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Charyn/Hurvitz, Treasures of the Empire of Evil - Screenplay, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Charyn, Color Print of, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - A Child's History of the Bronx - Sketch by Harry Hurvitz, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Cinema Booklets, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Cook, Mariana Portraits, 1986; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Cover Designs, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Darlin' Bill Cover Design, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Education in the New Age Booklet, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - George de Jerome Charyn, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Globe Hebdo, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Going to Jerusalem Promotional Lists, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Jefe, Book of Drawings, 1997; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Jerome Charyn - du Bronx dans le song, Bio-Bibliographie, 1997; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Lists (PEN, Sarah Lawrence College Meeting on Teaching Writing) (1966-1967), 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - L'o&il de la Lettre - Les Ecrivains des Etats-Unis - 1945 - 1994, 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Loustol, 10e Festival du Polar, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Loustol, Drawings for The Prince and Martin Mocha, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Maps and Booklets - Europe, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Maps and Booklets - Louisiana, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Maps and Booklets - New York, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Maps and Booklets - Texas, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Movie Proposal, author unknown (Oversized, Box 29), undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Mysteries of the Space Age, 1962; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Poster - The Paris Review (Oversized, Box 29), undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Purdy, James - Autobiography (Oversized, Box 29), undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - The Richard and Hilda Rosenthal Foundation Booklet, 1984; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Rajon, Florence "La Reception de Jerome Charyn ...", undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Rotbuch, Postcartoons, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Spatz, Ronald Wunderkind - Screenplay (based on Going to Jerusalem), undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Various Articles, photocopies, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Woolf, Michael 'Exploding the Genre: The Crime Fiction of Jerome Charyn", undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Works about Charyn, undated; 31142040613781 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Medals, undated (Box 29)
  - 1997, cuid6205; 1 item one collage (Item MSS.044.cuid6205)
    Scope and Contents
    Artist: Jean-Louis Fleury
    Collages (visual works)
- Oversized Materials
  - Series 3 Education and Employment Contracts, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Series 3 English Papers (2 of 2), undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Series 4 King Jude Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Series 7A Fiction Magazine The Pig Eaters, Two from Whalebone, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Series 7A Wochenpost #52 "Tod aller Dinge", undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Series 7A Zoom Magazine "Why is New York Changing faces?", undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Series 9 "Back to Bataan" Galleys (two of three), undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Series 9 "Back to Bataan" Galleys (three of three), undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Series 9 "Catfish Man" page proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Series 9 "Catfish Man" page proofs, first pass, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Series 9 "Darlin' Bill" page proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Series 9 "Death of a Tango King" page proofs, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Series 9 "The Frankling Scare" page proofs, master set, first pass, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Series 9 "Once Upon a Droshky" galleys, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Series 9 "Once Upon a Droshky" bound proof, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Series 9 "Secret Isaak" typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Series 9 "Secret Isaak" enclosures, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Series 9 "Secret Isaak" Part I typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Series 9 "The Seventh Babe" 1st pass, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Series 9 "The Seventh Babe" 2nd pass, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Series 10 "Good Policeman" call sheets, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Series 10 "Good Policeman" production reports, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Series 12 Festival of American Cinema in Paris, September 10, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Series 12 Miscellaneous, undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Series 12 "Semana Negra", undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Series 7C Max, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Series 7A "Les Nouvelles Litteraires" #6, 1986 (Box Flat 1, Folder data_value_missing_ddef54a5611390a7059a71b9b0f566d2)
  - Series 7B "Liberation", 1985 (Box Flat 1, Folder data_value_missing_04e1eddc8789242aded3e2267ec0b5a9)
  - Series 7B Life Magazine Daniel Stern review of "American Scrapbook", 1969 (Box Flat 1, Folder data_value_missing_71e5981ee13fcd6b11aa84ad4f706a17)
  - Series 7C Globe Hebado (Box Flat 1, Folder data_value_missing_51feb57bdf6c68760246d14e794c6196)
  - Series 14 "Bad Betty" booklet, article and letter (Box Flat 2, Folder data_value_missing_4ca0128d74bdffa954d6168b83944874)
  - Series 14 "Appelez-moi Malaussene" poster (Box Flat 2, Folder data_value_missing_0733580c5f855187eeb44769a07bc3fd)
  - Series 14 "Une Romance" poster (Box Flat 2, Folder data_value_missing_c1323784fbcf36df51b3d0d318af7b13)
  - Series 14 "Familyman" poster (Box Flat 2, Folder data_value_missing_c4b1460a598f9538861658a29647455a)
- Unprocessed Acc. 2005 .044 (Box 32, Box 33, Box 34, Box 35, Box 36, Box 37, Box 38, Box 39, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 50, Box 51, Box 52, Box 53, Box 54, Box 55, Box 56, Box 57, Box 58, Box 59, Box 60, Box 61, Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65)
- Unprocessed Acc. 2009.044 (Box 66)